gamegeniuses.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy – Game Genius

Gamegeniuses takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

Gamegeniuses does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or companies , except when we have your explicit permission (for example, to pass on your contact information when you have won a contest). You will not get on a spammer’s list because of your interactions with Gamegeniuses.

Gamegeniuses collects personal information when you register with Gamegeniuses, when you use Gamegeniuses products or services, when you visit Gamegeniuses pages or the pages of certain Gamegeniuses partners, and when you enter Gamegeniuses contests. Gamegeniuses may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Gamegeniuses and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Gamegeniuses collects information about your transactions with us.

Gamegeniuses automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Gamegeniuses cookie information, and the page you request.

Gamegeniuses uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and investigate abuse.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

Gamegeniuses reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. If we modify our Privacy Policy, we may post a notice on our website so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate user(s) to do otherwise.

We reserve the right to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of the Gamegeniuses Terms of Service, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.
